[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This US President, who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 2002, graduated from the United States Naval Academy in 1946.", "correct_answer": "James Carter", "incorrect_answers": ["Dwight Eisenhower", "Lyndon Johnson", "Gerald Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the documentary Grey Gardens, Edie shows a photograph of her younger days as a model and says that it hung in a very unusual place. Where?", "correct_answer": "In the elevator at Macys", "incorrect_answers": ["At the perfume counter in Tiffanys", "In the ladies room at Sax Fifth Avenue", "In the front window of Lord and Taylor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the following, which is a British rock band?", "correct_answer": "Deep Purple", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple Night", "24 Carat Purple", "Purpendicular"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of cells are Betz cells that are found in the human body?", "correct_answer": "Neurons", "incorrect_answers": ["Epithelial cells", "Striated muscle cells", "Melanocytes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There were three sequels to the first Home Alone movie prior to 2003.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island country whose capital is Nicosia is the third-largest Mediterranean island.", "correct_answer": "Cyprus", "incorrect_answers": ["Crete", "Malta", "Lesbos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the character Major Gen. Worden in The Dirty Dozen?", "correct_answer": "Ernest Borgnine", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee Marvin", "Jim Brown", "none of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Scream what kind of a store does Randy work at?", "correct_answer": "Video", "incorrect_answers": ["Candy", "Grocery", "Liquor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ursula Andress portrayed what character in the motion picture Dr. No?", "correct_answer": "Honey Ryder", "incorrect_answers": ["Natalya Simonova", "Tracy Draco", "Solitaire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a group of hyenas called?", "correct_answer": "Clan", "incorrect_answers": ["Pack", "Posse", "Giggle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The representatives of what guinea pig breed have extremely long hair that never stops growing all over their bodies?", "correct_answer": "Peruvian", "incorrect_answers": ["Teddy", "Texel", "Abyssinian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement concerning whales is true?", "correct_answer": "Some whales have one blow hole and some have two.", "incorrect_answers": ["All whales have two blow holes.", "Every whale has exactly one blow hole.", "Only some whales have blow holes."]}]